[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Can you quite believe you're in the green jacket on CNN, you know, talking to the world about being Masters champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "Talking to my favorite person.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 45, "question": "But can you believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 46, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "And that someone needs to take control of George Zimmerman in particular very quickly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "But are you encouraged by Angela Corey's statement just now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "We're encouraged, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Angela Corey"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 91, "question": "I mean how do you feel as Trayvon's mother seeing the man that killed your son, you know, thanking people over a Web site for the overwhelming support that he's receiving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "I really haven't viewed the Web site.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Trayvon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Not just for you and for the process of justice but also for George Zimmerman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I think it'll be a sense of relief on both ends.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Everything that's been discussed and debated, is it possible, knowing your son better than anybody, is it possible that Trayvon could have instigated the altercation with George Zimmerman and could have been potentially doing something to him that could have provoked him into thinking my life is in danger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "First and foremost, Piers, you have to understand the raising of Trayvon.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "NN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 137, "question": "What was your view as a lawyer of what went down today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 138, "answer": "Well, I was very upset and very disturbed as a criminal defense lawyer and as somebody who teaches professional responsibility to students.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 157, "question": "If there is no extension to the legal process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 158, "answer": "I don't know what may happen to his parents.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "Given her statement today, given the way this story has been developing, you'd be pretty amazed, would you, if this didn't now lead to at least an arrest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "I'd be surprised.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "John, we've had many a chat on this rock n' roll, rollercoaster ride, good times and bad times, how are you feeling tonight as his campaign manager?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "''", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": ": Well, holding my head high.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "What was the moment for you guys when you realized the game albeit temporarily is up?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "Well, you know, look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "She's back at home now, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "She is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Because presumably at some stage Rick Santorum having beaten Mitt Romney to a pulp with all he's got is going to have to turn around and say this guy should be president, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Does he hold out any aspiration of a potential VP slot or is that pie in the sky really, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "Well, look.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["November"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "There's no reason given his age that he couldn't revisit this and campaign again next time around, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CC", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Well, I think he's not going to look past November.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Is this the end of the race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "I mean when we get to the next stage of primaries, how significant are they now in light of Santorum pulling out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "They're not very significant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["hundreds of million of dollars"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "Presumably they're already planning the mother of all negative assaults on Romney, aren't they?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "If you think it was tough and angry and vicious among the Republican candidates themselves, just wait, Piers, because this is going to be a brutal, a brutal seven months with hundreds of million of dollars spent on both sides.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "You a golf fan, Wolf?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "I'm -- I watch the -- of course I'm not a huge player.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "Can I touch it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes, go ahead.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "How does it feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Feels nice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "To be Bubba Watson right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "It's overwhelming.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "But it's genuinely why, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Yes, for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "It's been a quite extraordinary time for you, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes, it has.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Why did you want that car so much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "The TV show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "But can you believe it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "The difficulty of the shot and how it played out, was that the moment for you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "No, I think the six-inch putt to win was the big moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What is it inside you that made you look down and say, I'm going for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "I trust everything in -- every ounce of my body, I trust it all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Other than don't conk it out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", "VB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "ATSON: Right, exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Or is it all just focused on the shot?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I definitely wasn't thinking about this show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Facebook"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "RP", ",", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 464, "question": "You weren't think of me when you won the Masters?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 465, "answer": "You know, I -- like I've always said, it's just -- this is -- this is to honor my parents, to honor my late dad, honor my grandparents, honor all the people that have gotten to this point in my life, my friends, some of the golfers that stayed around, some of the family members that were there, all my fans on Twitter, Facebook, all my fans across the world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "How much of his son are you, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "The first thing that springs to mind is he told me I got two options.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "How did you become so composed in such a pressurized moment, if the rest of the time you're all over the place?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "You know, I recognize that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "What lessons can you draw from that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Well, I think you got to learn from every situation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "Is he still the best you've seen, Tiger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 595, "question": "Bubba Watson, what were you thinking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "\"America's Got Talent.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bubba Watson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 601, "question": "What were you doing there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "What was the thought process?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "Golf is boring.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 647, "question": "What are they going to do?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 648, "answer": "I know who's not going to be a member.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "."], "qSentId": 649, "question": "Who, me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ",", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "You.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "What did she say to you when you became Masters champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "She said -- she didn't say much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 716, "question": "When he's old enough to focus?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "ORGAN: Yes, and --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 759, "question": "Did you make that yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 760, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "I don't know, how far is that, about five feet?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "About nine feet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 769, "question": "Oh, could be out of your range, couldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 770, "answer": "Yes, it could be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120410pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 779, "question": "What are you doing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 780, "answer": "Don't you worry about me, mate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]